https://www.girlguides.org.au/privacy-policy/

Girl Guides Australia > Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyGirl Guides Australia is committed to complying with the 13 Australian Privacy Principles (APP) as described in the Privacy Amendment (Enchancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012.The Board of Girl Guides Australia has endorsed a Privacy Policy to ensure that Girl Guides Australia are adhering to the Australian Privacy Principles.The intent of this policy is to ensure that the privacy of our members are respected and that personal information is appropriately protected.In developing its policy the Board addressed the following matters:Types of information collected – Personal;The way that Girl Guides collects and holds personal information;The purpose for which Girl Guides collects, hosts, uses and discloses personal information;Commercial Use of Data;The method by which a member of Girl Guides accesses personal information about them, that is held by GGA or a State Girl Guides Organisations and seek corrections to that information;Raising complaints;Disclosure of personal information to overseas recipients; andDeclaration of countries that we disclose information toThe policy can be downloaded here.Raising ConcernsIf you have a concern and/or complaint about Girl Guides Australia’s practice and policy when it comes to the Australian Privacy Principles please contact:The Complaints Officer (Privacy Policy) C/O CEO Girl Guides Australia The Hub Hyde Park 223 Liverpool St, Darlinghurst, NSW, 2010 Email: admin@girlguides.org.au Phone: 02 8328 0851In your correspondence please detail the nature of your concern and GGA will consider the nature of issues raised against the APP and our Policy. If required the concern can be escalated to the Privacy Commissioner.Join Girl GuidesValuable life skills for girls & young womenAustralian Capital TerritoryNew South WalesNorthern TerritoryQueenslandSouth AustraliaTasmaniaVictoriaWestern Australia MenuAboutHow Girl Guides worksGirl Guide Promise and LawCode of ConductGovernance & StrategyHow to JoinAs a GirlAs a Young WomanAs an Adult VolunteerTrefoil GuildProgramsAustralian Guide ProgramOlave ProgramRecognition of Girls and Young WomenInternational OpportunitiesGirl Guides Australia LEGO ® Friendship ChallengeNewsBushfire Emergency Relief FundResourcesProgram ResourcesGuide Lines and PoliciesUniformPost BoxWho we areBoardNational VolunteersNational Office TeamContact Us
LoginLeaders & managers
Contact us1300 GIRL GUIDES
MenuSearch Girl Guides Australia
ContactAbout Girl Guides
